Samuel Dash Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Consultations and Cases, 1897-2003 (Box 1-57)
  - Hughes v. State (Box 30)
    - General case material, 1980-1985, undated
    - Interviews, 1980
  - Hulsey, Paul, consultation, 1999 (Box 31)
  - Independent Counsel Act
    - Background information, 1905, 1976-1981, 1988-1998, undated, (3 folders)
    - Correspondence and testimonies
      - 1987-1992, (3 folders)
      - 1993, 1999, undated, (3 folders) (Box 32)
    - Drafts and notes, 1992-1993, undated
  - Ingersoll, Buchanan, consultation, 1987
  - Iron Mountain, Inc., cases, 1999-2002, (3 folders)
  - Kleinkopf, Kent, consultation,1975
  - Loeb, Murray, consultation, 1971
  - Lyles v. Argenbright Sec., 2002, undated
  - Marcucci v. City of Philadelphia See Container 15, Banks v. Levy (Box 33)
  - Masiello v. United States, 1968-1973, undated, (2 folders)
  - McDermott v. Philadelphia Newspapers
    - General case material, 1973, 1979, 1986-1988, undated
    - Transcript, 1986
  - Michigan Attorney Grievance Commission, 1986-1989, undated
  - Miscellany, 1976-1986, 1994-2003
  - Muhammad, Murad See Container 23, Don King Prods. v. Ruddock
  - Nash, Jeffrey L., consultation, 2002-2003, undated
  - National Association of Security Dealers/Nasdaq Stock Market representation
    - Background information
      - Cases
        - 1941, 1955-1975
        - 1981-1995, (2 folders) (Box 34)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1993-1996, undated
    - General case material, 1992-1996
  - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union, 1991-1993, undated
  - One Meridian Place fire See Container 1, Aetna Casualty & Surety Co. v. E/R Assocs.
  - Orpiano v. Shields, 1982
  - Passaic fire litigation See Container 1, A.L.U. Textile Combing Corp. v. Texaco Chem. Corp.
  - In re Pérez-Giménez, 1987, undated
  - Pierce Leahy Corp. v. Principal Shareholders See Container 32, Iron Mountain, Inc., cases
  - Pittsburgh Corning Corp. See Containers 2-10, Asbestos litigation cases
  - Rose v. Giamatti
    - Background information
      - Cases, 1956, 1965, 1972-1986, undated, (2 folders)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1989 (Box 35)
    - Exhibits
      - Lettered, 1988-1989
      - Numbered, circa 1989, (2 folders)
    - General case material, 1989-1990, 2003, undated, (4 folders)
    - Notes, 1989, undated
    - Preliminary statement, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Report to commissioner, 1989
      - Exhibits, (2 folders)
      - Text, (3 folders)
  - St. John Parish See Container 23, Convention of the Episcopal Diocese v. Minwax Co.
  - Schubot v. Levenstein
    - Background information and notes, 1995-1996, undated
    - Case summary, undated
    - Depositions (Box 37)
      - Braccialarghe, Randolph, 1995
      - Brown, Harold, 1995, (2 folders)
      - Heimberg, Frederick M. 1994
      - Horkan, James Timothy, 1994
      - Levenstein, Richard, 1991
    - Exhibits, undated
    - General case material, 1990-1996, undated, (2 folders) (Box 38)
    - Pleadings, 1991
  - Scott v. United States, 1975-1978, undated, (4 folders)
  - Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1989-1990, undated, (3 folders) (Box 39)
  - Seymour v. Ball
    - Depositions
      - Ball, G. Thomas, 1996, (3 folders)
      - Harris, Neal W., 1996
      - Seymour, Michael, 1994, (2 folders) (Box 40)
    - Exhibits, plaintiffs, 1996
      - Nos. 1-85, (4 folders)
      - Nos. 86-97 (Box 41)
    - General case material, 1994-1997
    - Transcripts, 1995-1996
  - Sheet Metal Occupational Health Institute, 1988-1991, undated
  - In re Shenker, 1985-1987
  - Silent Coup See Container 23, Dean v. St. Martin's Press
  - Smith Clothing Manufacturing Co., 1977
  - In re Sofaer
    - Background information, undated
    - General case material
      - 1995
      - 1996-1999, undated, (4 folders) (Box 42)
    - Pleadings, circa 1997
      - Vol. 1
      - Vols. 2-3, (2 folders) (Box 43)
    - Respondents list of exhibits, 1995
  - State v. Thornton (Box 44)
    - Background information and notes, 1953, 1972, 1977-1987, undated, (2 folders)
    - General case material, 1987-1988
  - Stonegate Elementary School and Paul E. Tubin, 1981, 1991-1993, undated
  - In re Swift, 1992-1993
  - Thomson Consumer Elecs. v. Anchor Glass Container Corp.
    - Background information, 1949-1950, 1966-1967, 1977, 1986-1995, undated
    - General case material
      - 1993
      - 1995-1996, undated, (4 folders) (Box 45)
  - Tobacco litigation cases
    - Background information and notes, 1985, 1991-2001, undated
    - Brown & Williamson Tobacco Corp. rebuttal, undated
    - Exhibits, undated
    - General case material
      - 1994
      - 1995-2000, (5 folders) (Box 46)
      - 2001, (2 folders) (Box 47)
      - 2002-2003, undated
  - United Nations, interregional meeting of experts on crime, 1977-1981, undated, (2 folders)
  - United States v. Curran
    - Argument and summary, undated
    - Background information
      - Articles and clippings, 1977, 1983, 1994
      - Cases, 1897, 1932, 1941, 1960, 1978-1980, 1988-1993, (2 folders)
      - Conspiracy, 1986-1992, undated (Box 48)
      - Federal election campaigns, undated
      - Fraud and false statements, 1948, 1966, 1975-1990
      - Issues of statutory construction and interpretation
        - Doctrine of primary jurisdiction, 1980, 1988-1993
        - General versus specific statutes, 1979-1986, undated
        - Overlapping statutes, 1982-1985
      - Principles, 1973-1993, undated, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 49)
    - Exhibits, undated
      - Defendant, (2 folders)
      - Government
    - General case material
      - 1992, (2 folders)
      - 1993, (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box 50)
      - 1994, undated, (5 folders) (Box 51)
    - Joint appendix, 1993
      - Vol. 1
      - Vol. 2 (Box 52)
    - Notes, 1994, undated
    - Transcripts
      - 1992, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 53)
      - 1993, (3 folders)
  - United States v. Goldberg See Container 26, In re Extradition of Mann (Box 54)
  - United States v. Rodriquez-Orejuela
    - Background information and notes, 1977, 1987-1996
    - General case material, 1995-1997, (2 folders)
  - United States v. Sweig, 1971
  - University of Georgia Research Found. v. Oblon, Fisher, Spivak, McClelland & Maier, P.C., 1986-1987, undated
  - Useden v. Acker
    - Background information and notes, 1985-1988, undated
    - Exhibits
      - 1981
      - 1982-1988, undated, (5 folders) (Box 55)
    - General case material
      - 1986-1987
      - 1988, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 56)
  - Wells v. Liddy, 2002
  - Wells Dairy v. American Indus. Refrigeration, 2001, (2 folders)
  - Wilson v. Geldner
    - Background information, 1993
    - General case material, 1993-1995, undated, (4 folders) (Box 57)
  - Wimbrow v. Council of Unit Owners, 2003
  - Woodward v. Myrtle Beach Hosp., 1979, 1992, 1998, undated, (3 folders)
  - Zurcher v. Stanford Daily, 1978-1979, undated, (2 folders)
- Government Investigations, 1951-2003 (Box 58-104)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, newspaper clippings, statements, testimony, transcripts, depositions, printed matter, and legal briefs pertaining to government investigations in which Dash served as an investigator or consultant.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of investigation and therein by topic, type of material, or name of person or organization.
  - Alaska state senate, impeachment inquiry of Governor Bill Sheffield (Box 58)
    - Background information
      - Articles by Dash and others, 1955, 1985-1987
      - Contracting statutes and regulations, 1985
      - Impeachment
        - Printed matter, 1974, 1981-1985
        - Review, 1985
          - Appendices A-C, (3 folders)
          - Text (Box 59)
      - Printed matter, 1985-1986, (2 folders)
      - Purchasing regulations, policies, and procedures, 1982
      - Sheffield, Bill, schedules and logs, 1984-1985
    - Exhibits, grand jury, 1985, (2 folders)
    - General case material
      - 1985, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 60)
      - 1986
    - Interviews, 1985, undated
    - Miscellany, undated
    - Newspaper clippings, 1985, undated, (5 folders)
    - Notes and questions (Box 61)
      - Others, 1984-1986, undated, (3 folders)
      - Sheffield, Bill, 1983-1985, undated
    - Report of grand jury with corrections, 1985
    - Statements, 1985
      - Herman, Laurie
      - Jackson, David Barry
      - McBirney, N. Derrall
      - Petersen, Richard G. (Box 62)
      - Rudd, Lisa
      - Sheffield, Bill
      - Shively, John T.
      - Staack, Anselm
    - Summaries of testimony, 1985
    - Tape logs of grand jury proceedings, 1985
      - Apr. 24-May 6
      - May 7-July 2, (3 folders) (Box 63)
    - Transcripts
      - Grand jury, 1985
        - Exhibits
        - Text
          - Vol. I
          - Vols. II-IV, (3 folders) (Box 64)
          - Vols. V-VII, (3 folders) (Box 65)
          - Vols. VIII-X, (3 folders) (Box 66)
          - Vols. XI-XII (Box 67)
      - Senate Rules Committee, 1985
        - Corrections
        - Listings and schedules
        - Text
          - July 22-July 23, (4 folders)
          - July 24-July 27, (6 folders) (Box 68)
          - July 29-July 31, (5 folders) (Box 69)
          - Aug. 1, (1 folder) (Box 70)
          - Aug. 2-3, (2 folders)
  - Cerro Maravilla investigation, Puerto Rico
    - Article by Dash, undated
    - Background information
      - Attorney-client privilege waived by codefendant, 1989
      - Fraudulent concealment/statute of limitations, 1979-1989, (3 folders)
      - Immunity from prosecution, 1951, 1980-1989 (Box 71)
      - Miscellany, undated
      - Preparation for meeting in San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1987
      - Speech and debate clause, 1964-1973, 1980, (2 folders)
      - Statements, Julio Ortiz Molina, 1978
    - Correspondence and memoranda
      - 1979-1985, (2 folders)
      - 1987-1996, (4 folders) (Box 72)
    - Days, Drew, interview, 1990, (2 folders) (Box 73)
    - Documents
      - Groups I-III, 1977-1978, (3 folders)
      - Numbered, undated (Box 74)
        - Nos. 1-64, 254-259, (3 folders)
        - Miscellaneous
    - Exhibits, undated
      - A-F
      - DD1-DD39
    - Freedom of Information Act request
      - Background information and notes, 1986-1990
      - General case material
        - 1985
        - 1987-1988, (6 folders) (Box 75)
        - 1989, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 76)
        - 1990-1991, undated, (3 folders)
    - Index and abstracts of documents, undated, (3 folders) (Box 77)
    - Litigation notebooks, undated
      - Books 1-2, (2 folders)
      - Book 3 (Box 78)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1979-1992, (4 folders)
    - Notes
      - 1985-1992, (2 folders)
      - Undated (Box 79)
    - Outline for hearings, 1987-1991, undated, (2 folders)
    - “Outline of Evidence Gathered in the Senatorial Investigation of the Events of Cerro Maravilla, 1984-1990,” 1990
    - Printed matter, 1983-1989
    - Senate of Puerto Rico ex rel. Judiciary Comm. v. United States Dep't of Justice See Containers 74-76, Freedom of Information Act request
  - Watergate Affair (Box 80)
    - Appointment logs for John Mitchell and John Ehrlichman, 1971-1973
    - Chronological reports, 1971-1974, (2 folders)
    - Chronological sequence of events, 1971
    - “Comparison of Passages from “Transcripts of Eight Recorded Presidential Conversations” and “Submission of Recorded Presidential Conversations,” 1974
    - Correspondence
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1973-1975, (2 folders)
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1973-1974, (7 folders) (Box 81)
      - Condolences, 1973-1974, (3 folders) (Box 82)
      - Congratulatory, 1973, (4 folders)
      - “C” miscellaneous
        - 1973, (4 folders)
        - 1974, (3 folders) (Box 83)
      - “D” miscellaneous
        - 1973, (4 folders)
        - 1974, (2 folders) (Box 84)
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1973-1976, (2 folders)
      - “F” miscellaneous, 1973-1974, (6 folders)
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1973-1974, (5 folders) (Box 85)
      - “H” miscellaneous
        - 1973, (3 folders)
        - 1974, (3 folders) (Box 86)
      - “I” miscellaneous, 1973-1974
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1973-1974, (4 folders)
      - “K” miscellaneous
        - 1973, (1 folder) (Box 87)
        - 1974
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1973-1974, (3 folders)
      - “M” miscellaneous
        - 1973, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 88)
        - 1974, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 89)
        - 1977
      - “N” miscellaneous, 1973-1974
      - “O” miscellaneous, 1973-1974
      - “P” miscellaneous, 1973-1974, (2 folders)
      - “Q” miscellaneous, 1973
      - “R” miscellaneous, 1973-1976, undated, (6 folders) (Box 90)
      - “S” miscellaneous
        - 1973
        - 1974-1975, (4 folders) (Box 91)
      - “T” miscellaneous, 1973-1974
      - “W” miscellaneous, 1974, undated
      - “Y” miscellaneous, 1973
      - Unidentified, 1974, undated
    - Exhibits, 1970-1973 See also Top Secret
    - Interview files, 1973
      - File no. 1, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 92)
      - File no. 2, (4 folders)
      - File no. 3, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 93)
      - Miscellany
    - Legal documents, 1973-1974, (3 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1973-1974, 1983, undated, (2 folders)
    - Newspaper clippings and press releases
      - 1972
      - 1973, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 94)
      - 1974-1975, 1992-2003, undated
    - Notes and drafts, 1973, undated
    - Photographs, 1974, undated
    - Senate Select Committee on Presidential Activities
      - Inventory of files, undated, (2 folders)
      - Minutes, 1973-1974, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 95)
      - Reports, 1973-1979, undated, (2 folders)
      - Staff roster, 1973-1974
    - Telephone logs and numbers, 1973, undated
    - Watergate Reorganization and Reform Act of 1975, 1975-1976, undated, (4 folders)
  - Whitewater Inquiry (Box 96)
    - Background information, 1975-1998, undated, (6 folders)
    - Bills and contracts for services, 1994-1998
    - Charts and chronologies, 1986-1998
    - General case material (Box 97)
      - 1993-1994, (2 folders)
      - 1995
        - Jan.-July, (4 folders)
        - Aug., (2 folders) (Box 98)
        - Sept., (2 folders)
        - Oct., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 99)
        - Nov.-Dec., (3 folders)
      - 1996
        - Jan.-July, (3 folders)
        - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 100)
      - 1997, (6 folders)
      - 1998 (Box 101)
        - Jan.-July, (7 folders)
        - Aug.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 102)
      - 1999-2000, undated, (2 folders)
    - Letters from the public
      - 1994-1997
      - 1998-1999 (Box 103)
    - Newspaper clippings and press releases
      - 1993-1998, (7 folders)
      - 1999-2002, undated (Box 104)
    - Notes, 1994-1998, undated
    - “Privilege Log: Documents Withheld from Production to the Independent Counsel Pursuant to Subpoena,” 1995
    - “Report on the Death of Vincent M. Foster, Jr., by the Office of Independent Counsel In re: Madison Guaranty Savings & Loan Association,” 1997
    - Rose Law Firm
      - Key entities, events, and individuals, 1998
      - Summary of conflicts, circa 1998
    - “Treasury/White House Contacts Regarding Madison Guaranty Savings and Loan,” 1994
- Organizations and Committees, 1764-2003 (Box 105-179)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, minutes, financial records, newspaper clippings, notes, drafts, and printed matter.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization or committee and therein by topic or type of material.
  - American Bar Association (Box 105)
    - Center for Professional Responsibility See Containers 109-110, Ethics 2000 Commission
    - Commission on Advertising
      - Correspondence, 1985-1988, (3 folders)
      - Meetings
        - 1985, Oct.
        - 1986
          - Feb.-Apr., (2 folders)
          - Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 106)
        - 1987
          - Mar.-Oct., (3 folders)
          - Dec. (Box 107)
        - circa 1987
        - 1988, (3 folders)
        - 1989, (2 folders) (Box 108)
      - Public hearings conference, 1986
    - Ethics 2000 Commission (Box 109)
      - General, 1995-1998
      - Meetings, 1998, (6 folders)
      - Rules, 2000
        - Comments
        - Numbers (Box 110)
        - Scienter Subcommittee, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1969-1972, 1993, 2001-2002
    - Project on Minimum Standards for Criminal Justice
      - Correspondence and drafts
        - 1966
          - May
          - July-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 111)
        - 1967, (2 folders)
        - 1968
          - Jan.-Mar.
          - Apr.-Sept., (2 folders) (Box 112)
          - No month
        - Undated, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 113)
      - Printed matter, 1966-1968, undated, (2 folders)
    - Rule 4.2/ABA Model Rules of Professional Conduct
      - Case summary, undated
      - Cases
        - 1941, 1951, 1959-1976
        - 1979-1992, (6 folders) (Box 114)
        - 1993, undated, (2 folders) (Box 115)
      - Correspondence
        - circa 1988
        - 1989-1995, (7 folders)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 116)
      - Notes, 1993, undated
      - Printed matter, 1981, 1990-1995, undated, (3 folders)
      - Reports and writings
        - 1989-1994
        - Undated, (1 folder) (Box 117)
    - Section of Criminal Justice
      - General
        - 1967-1986, (5 folders)
        - 1987
          - Jan.-Feb.
          - Mar.-June, (6 folders) (Box 118)
          - July-Dec. (Box 119)
          - No month
        - 1988
          - Jan.-Mar., (3 folders)
          - Apr.-Aug., (9 folders) (Box 120)
          - Sept.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 121)
          - No month
        - 1989
          - Jan.-May, (4 folders)
          - June-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 122)
          - No month
        - 1990 (Box 123)
          - Jan.-July, (7 folders)
          - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 124)
        - 1991
          - Jan.-Aug., (6 folders)
          - Nov.-Dec. (Box 125)
          - No month, (2 folders)
        - 1992
          - Jan.-July, (4 folders)
          - Aug.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 126)
        - 1993
          - Jan.-Dec., (5 folders)
          - No month
        - 1994-1995, undated, (6 folders) (Box 127)
      - Notes, 1975, 1986-1988, undated
    - Section of Criminal Law (Box 128)
      - Board of Governor's special meeting, 1970
        - D.C. Crime Bill
        - General
        - Organized Crime Bill, (2 folders)
      - Electronic surveillance, 1966-1971, undated, (2 folders)
      - General (Box 129)
        - 1968
        - 1969
          - Jan.-Oct., (5 folders)
          - Nov. (Box 130)
        - 1970
        - 1971
          - Jan.-Mar., (5 folders)
          - Apr.-Nov (Box 131)
          - No month
        - 1972, 1979, undated, (2 folders)
      - Meetings, London, England, 1970-1971, (3 folders)
    - Section of International Law and Practice, Central and East European Law Initiative, 1992-1995, 2002
    - Section of Tort and Insurance Practice, Committee on the Professional Independence of the Lawyer, 1984-1987, undated, (2 folders)
    - Standing Committee on Ethics and Professional Responsibility (Box 132)
      - General
        - 1980-1984
        - 1985
          - Jan.-Nov., (6 folders)
          - Dec. (Box 133)
        - 1986, (4 folders)
        - 1987
          - Jan.-Dec., (2 folders)
          - No month (Box 134)
        - 1988-2003, undated, (7 folders)
      - Meeting agenda books (Box 135)
        - 1984, Oct., (2 folders)
        - 1985
          - Feb., (3 folders)
          - Apr.-Oct., (4 folders) (Box 136)
        - 1986
          - Feb., (2 folders)
          - Apr.-Aug., (5 folders) (Box 137)
          - Oct., (3 folders) (Box 138)
        - 1987
          - Feb., (2 folders)
          - May, (1 folder) (Box 139)
          - Aug., (4 folders)
          - Nov., (2 folders) (Box 140)
        - 1988
          - Feb., (4 folders)
          - Apr.-Aug., (6 folders) (Box 141)
          - Oct., (5 folders) (Box 142)
        - 1989, Aug., (2 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1985 (Box 143)
      - Rationales used by individual jurisdictions in support of amendments to specific model rules, 1986
      - Surreptitious recordings, 1936, 1968, 1974-1989
      - Workshop on Lawyers' Professional Responsibility, 1984, (3 folders)
    - Standing Committee on Law and National Security, 1980-1985
  - American Jewish Committee, Washington, D.C., chapter, 1973-1979
  - American University School of Law, Washington, D.C., American Medal of Justice, 1978
  - Citizens' Committee on Watergate Reform, 1978 (Box 144)
  - Common Cause
    - 1977
    - 1978
      - Jan.-Apr., (6 folders)
      - May-Nov., (3 folders) (Box 145)
    - 1979-1981, undated, (2 folders)
  - Democratic National Council, Democratic Policy Committee, 1971-1972
  - Divi Hotels
    - Board of Directors
      - Audit Committee
        - Meetings and minutes
          - 1986-1988
          - 1989, undated (Box 146)
        - Notes, 1986-1989, undated
        - Reports
          - Director of finance, 1988-1989
          - Ernst & Whinney, 1988
          - Monthly consolidated, 1988-1989
      - General
        - List of members, 1988
        - Meetings and minutes, 1984-1988, undated (Box 147)
        - Reports
          - Corporate update, 1989
          - Nine-month summary of performance, 1989
          - Quarterly
            - 1987
            - 1988, (1 folder) (Box 148)
            - 1989
    - General correspondence
      - 1982-1987, (2 folders)
      - 1988-1990, (3 folders) (Box 149)
    - Subject file
      - Annual and quarterly reports, 1985-1990
      - Articles of association, amendments, 1987
      - Asset and stock agreements, plans, policies, and reports
        - 1984-1987, (3 folders)
        - 1988-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 150)
      - Brochure, undated
      - Casino license application, Puerto Rico, 1987
      - Corporate directorship practices, 1975-1988, (2 folders)
      - Directors, employees, and officials, 1984-1988
      - Engagement letters, 1987-1988
      - Executive
        - Compensation review, 1988
        - Employment agreements, 1988
        - Retreat, undated
      - Flamingo Beach Club, 1983
      - Gulliver's World Ltd., 1987
      - Income and expense reports and statements, 1986-1988
      - Management letters, 1986-1988 (Box 151)
      - Minutes, executive and shareholder meetings, 1984-1985
      - Miscellany, 1986-1988
      - Notes, 1986-1990, undated
      - Projected construction budget, undated
      - Projected occupancy for Divi Hotel properties, 1987
      - Proxys, 1985-1989
      - Ramada Inn purchase
        - Correspondence
          - 1987-1988, (3 folders)
          - 1989 (Box 152)
        - Documents, 1986
        - Due diligence report, 1987
  - Georgetown University Law Center, Institute of Criminal Law and Procedure, Washington, D.C. See also Containers 165-173, Judicial Conference of the District of Columbia Circuit, Committee on Laws Pertaining to Mental Disorders; and Container 173, Legal Aid Agency of the District of Columbia
    - Criminal Law Research Conference
      - 1967-1968, (2 folders)
      - 1969, undated (Box 153)
    - Di Gianngiemo, Leo A., 1967, undated
    - Federal Bonding Program, 1985-1986, undated
    - General, 1965-1988, undated, (3 folders)
    - Judicial Conference Committee on the Administration of Justice Under Emergency Conditions, 1971
    - Policy Board meeting, undated
    - Program statement, 1966
    - Projects and proposals
      - Analysis of recidivist sentencing laws, 1985-1986
      - Appellate Litigation Clinic
        - 1973, 1981
        - 1982-1983, undated, (2 folders) (Box 154)
      - Children's Bureau, 1966
      - Chromatographic analysis, 1967
      - Community health centers and the law, 1966-1967
      - Comparative pretrial release, 1968, 1974
      - Criminal prosecution: policy choices in organizing the accusatory and adjudicative processes, 1988
      - Defendant interview, 1966